<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>An AI assistant for devops on Roboweb</title><link>http://roboweb.app/</link><description>Recent content in An AI assistant for devops on Roboweb</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 15:43:09 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://roboweb.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kubernetes</title><link>http://roboweb.app/docs/k8s/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 09:49:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://roboweb.app/docs/k8s/</guid><description>This quickstart shows you how to start JupyterLab with the Roboweb extension on Kubernetes using our public docker image
us-west1-docker.pkg.dev/roboweb-images/roboweb-images/jupyterlab:v0.0.5 This docker image contains JupyterLab with the Roboweb extension already installed. It is based on Kubeflow&amp;rsquo;s JupyterLab image and thus should be deployable inside Kubeflow.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have Kubeflow, you can use the minimal Kubernetes manifest in [jlewi/roboweb-docs/k8s/manifests]https://github.com/jlewi/roboweb-docs/tree/main/k8s/manifests).
Clone the jlewi/roboweb-docs repository
git clone https://github.com/jlewi/roboweb-docs.git Note As is this manifest isn&amp;rsquo;t intended for doing meaningful work inside JupyterLab.</description></item><item><title>Quickstart</title><link>http://roboweb.app/docs/quickstart/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 09:49:12 -0700</pubDate><guid>http://roboweb.app/docs/quickstart/</guid><description>Install the JupyterLab Extension Install the extensions
python -m pip install roboweb-extension python -m pip install roboweb-server Activate the extension
python -m jupyter serverextension enable --py roboweb_server Configure the Extension To use the extension start jupyter lab.
jupyter-lab In the right hand navigation window click the roboweb icon. This will open up the roboweb extension in the right half of the screen.
The Roboweb assistant should appear in the right hand side toolbar in JupyterLab.</description></item><item><title>Terms</title><link>http://roboweb.app/terms/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 12:23:00 -0800</pubDate><guid>http://roboweb.app/terms/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>